All right, let's start talking
about the last quest.
You've worked so hard
on your quests so far.
Only the last quest remains.
We will reveal the final quest.
The final quest is…
Jirisan. Climbing this is the final quest.
-Yeah.
-Congratulations!
I saw it coming.
Yeah, I knew this would happen.
I was wondering why
it hadn't shown up yet.
CHEONWANGBONG PEAK
JIRISAN MOUNTAIN
THE ETERNAL FIXTURE
OF KOREA'S SOUTHERN END
NESTLED WITHIN THE MOUNTAINS
STRETCHING FROM THE EAST TO THE WEST
AND FEATURING CASCADING WATERFALLS
IS KOREA'S FIRST NATIONAL PARK
AND THE HIGHEST PEAK OF JIRISAN
CHEONWANGBONG
THE KOREAN SPIRIT AROSE FROM HERE
THE PLACE ABOVE THE CLOUDS
WHERE YOU CAN LOOK DOWN
ON THE MOUNTAINS AND RIVERS
IT CONNECTS PEOPLE WITH NATURE
AND THE EARTH WITH THE SKY
THE SACRED MOUNTAIN
OF THE KOREAN PEOPLE, JIRISAN
The mission is simple this time.
The goal is to just reach Cheonwangbong.
How high is it?
CHEONWANGBONG IS 1,915 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
It's as high as Hallasan.
SECOND TALLEST MOUNTAIN IN KOREA
But I heard it takes longer than a day
to reach the top.
THEY WILL HIKE A TRAIL
THAT TAKES LESS THAN A DAY
That must've been a different trail then.
I'd like an easy route so we can enjoy it.
We want to appreciate the scenery,
so let us take an easy trail.
But if it's for two days, will we relax
and rest on the first day as usual?
Should we do some activities?
Sure, we don't mind.
But you might end up losing your gold.
NO WAY
Let's leave all our gold at home.
EXTREME MEASURES
We understand. Let's wrap up for today.
-Good work, everyone!
-Thank you!
THEIR OFFICIAL COMMITMENTS IN ULSAN END
THAT EVENING
I'll count on you to make
something delicious, Mom.
THE NEXT MORNING
AT THE YEONGNAM ALPS BASE CAMP
We'll see you there.
THEY VISIT TARZZAN'S PARENTS
FOR THE SEOLLAL HOLIDAY
THEY GO TO DOWNTOWN ULSAN
Then, let's buy some fruit
and a red ginseng gift set.
Sounds good.
A gift set of health products
and a gift set of fruits.
STRONG HOLIDAY VIBES
-Hello.
THEY ARRIVE AT A DEPARTMENT STORE
These red ginseng supplements are good.
-This?
-That's right.
-Okay, let's get this one.
-One of these?
-We'll take this one.
-Okay.
His house is very close.
-Really? Is that so?
-Yes.
HEALTH SUPPLEMENT PURCHASE IS COMPLETE
This one?
-One of these.
-That's perfect.
Let's get this one.
This one. We'll take this one.
I feel rather bad.
THE BEST ONE WITHOUT HESITATION
-Do you want to pay in installments?
-No, it's okay.
THE OLDER MEMBERS BUY THE GIFTS
WITH THEIR OWN MONEY
You guys spent too much.
It's okay. We should do things right.
THEY HEAD TO MEET TARZZAN'S PARENTS
WITH A TRUNK FULL OF GIFTS
THEY ARRIVE AT TARZZAN'S HOUSE
NOW THAT THEY'RE HERE,
THEY FEEL NERVOUS AND EXCITED
My heart's beating fast.
-It smells delicious.
-I smell food.
It smells like fancy food.
Maybe pasta?
CAN ALWAYS SMELL FOOD
IN THE HALLWAYS DURING THE HOLIDAYS
-Hey, Chae-min, you go in first.
-What?
You go in first. You're the most handsome.
Right, you should enter first.
-Hello.
TARZZAN'S FATHER
-Hi, Auntie.
THEY ENTER TARZZAN'S PARENTS' HOUSE
-Hello, ma'am.
-Hello.
-Come on in.
-Lee Chae-min?
-Yes.
-Nice to meet you.
Car, the garden? Nice to meet you.
TARZZAN'S MOTHER
Hello.
-Dowoon of DAY6.
-Hello.
I've been enjoying your show.
Thank you so much.
-Hello.
Wait, here's the person
we wanted to see the most.
-Hello, Producer Nah.
-Hello.
-Come on in.
-Please come in.
-We brought some things.
-It's not much, but…
Thank you so much.
Gosh, they prepared a lot of food for us.
TARZZAN'S HOUSE REVEALED
FOR THE FIRST TIME
-Let me introduce his aunt.
-I see. His aunt.
INTRODUCING THE FAMILY
That's Chae-won's aunt.
TARZZAN'S AUNT
-Hello.
I'm helping out for the day.
Do you think I take after my mom or dad?
Looking at you now,
your eyes and nose resemble your dad's.
-You're right.
-Yes.
TARZZAN'S DAD
And the lower half of your face
resembles your mom.
Especially your lips.
TARZZAN'S MOM
Hey, look at his photos.
-Look.
-He's so cute.
He's adorable.
Hey, take a look at his hairstyle here.
Hey, it looks good. It looks good on him.
He was handsome as a kid too.
You look exactly the same.
AGES 14, 6, 16, 18
What is this? Power Rangers Mystic Force?
He must've been in a play.
He went to see the musical.
So cute.
This next room is mine.
-Is this your room?
-Yes.
-We left it as it was.
-You like this stuff?
Well, it was my favorite stuffed animal
since I was little.
PRODUCER NAH LOOKS AROUND TARZZAN'S ROOM
Would you like to see his old diary?
Come on, Mom!
-His diary.
-No, you can't.
Hold on. Where is his diary, ma'am?
PRODUCER NAH HAS FOUND HIS TARGET
-Where are they?
-Here.
-Seriously…
-All of these?
I told you to hide them.
Yes, here's his diary.
His handwriting is good.
"On the first day of sixth grade,
Lee Dong-hyeok told me
that Ms. Kim Young-kyung is nice."
"That made my palms so sweaty."
-What does that mean?
Why were you scared of your teacher?
Did you do something bad?
-In sixth grade?
-I think so.
Where should we sit?
NOW THAT THEY'VE FINISHED THE TOUR,
IT'S TIME TO EAT
-Is this sukiyaki?
-Yes.
What a fancy dish.
I made these this morning.
HOMEMADE SUKIYAKI MADE BY TARZZAN'S MOM
BEEF JEON AND SHRIMP JEON SHE MADE HERSELF
AND NOTICE THAT THE JEON
WAS MADE WITH SIRLOIN
Thank you for the food, ma'am.
-Thank you.
Sure thing.
You should try the jeon first.
-Okay.
-I'll give it a taste.
Thank you. Please go first.
A BITE WITH FRESH KIMCHI
YUM
Thank you so much.
Gosh, it's really good. Have some.
How did she make it so flat?
NOW IT'S TIME TO TRY THE SUKIYAKI
This is a top-tier dish.
DIPS IT INTO A RAW EGG AND TAKES A BITE
Gosh, I feel so good.
-You dip it into this, right?
-It's good.
Actually, my second favorite dish
after pork cutlets is sukiyaki.
Seriously. This is so good.
The tyrant from Bon Appétit, Your Majesty
says it's delicious.
It's really good.
-Thank you.
-Seriously.
-You've eaten this since you were little?
-Yes.
Really? This must be
one of her best dishes.
Since I did sports,
I needed to find food
that was healthy and delicious,
so I liked dishes like this.
This is so good.
-Goodness, there's also rice.
-Yes.
My goodness.
We heard you didn't have breakfast.
That's right.
Tarzzan couldn't eat
because he woke up a bit late.
TARZZAN'S MOM'S ABALONE RICE
Is there anyone here
you were curious about?
There are fans among the people I know.
-Right.
-They asked me to get autographs for them.
I mean, it's hard to even get
an autograph from my son.
IT'S HARD TO SEE HER BUSY SON
I guess you can't see your parents often.
No.
He said he has to work
throughout the holidays this year too.
I know.
Has Tarzzan ever given you a hard time?
He's a good son.
-My son's nice.
-Yes, he's so nice.
I don't think he'd ever cause trouble.
I got a call once
that he got hurt outside.
While playing rough outside?
-Yes.
-And he made you worried sick.
Exactly.
He went to the park on his own,
and they said he got hurt.
I got hurt while going
to Ulsan Grand Park alone.
By the way, yesterday,
Tarzzan took us
to all of his favorite places.
From the milmyeon place to the park.
Really?
By the way, who decided
on having lunch here today?
Who planned it?
THE PRESIDENT DID
I wish he'd discussed it with us.
Wait, we thought he'd told you beforehand.
-I did tell you.
-He called me at 6:00 p.m. yesterday.
-Yesterday afternoon?
-Yes.
He said, "Mom, eight people
are coming at 1:00 p.m. tomorrow."
How many times did I tell you
to call in advance?
I did. I told you in advance
that we were coming.
Yeah, at 6:00 p.m. yesterday!
So I was worried
that there wouldn't be enough food.
-It is enough.
-It's enough. It's so good.
Now that I've met his parents, I can tell.
-He had a very happy childhood.
-Right.
I can feel it.
I could tell he received
a lot of love growing up.
-When I'd talk with him.
-Right.
It seems he's received too much love
so we're trying to make him
a better person.
We noticed some things
that needed improvement.
We're correcting them.
That way, he can become a global star.
Thank you.
We're already imagining his future
three years from now.
-Right.
-We're thinking how he'll be.
Chae-min's been sharing rooms
with him often.
-He's keeping close tabs.
-We've slept together often.
They have a lot in common.
Like that K-Arts paper on the fridge.
Mine's put up at my home too.
FAMILIAR PAPER TO A FELLOW ALUMNUS
You still keep
the admission letter on the fridge?
Yes, I can't throw it away.
You just can't.
Right, because it's K-Arts.
Because once you print it out,
you can't print it out again.
My parents printed mine out
and laminated it.
-Right.
-So it won't wear out.
ADMISSION LETTER
MAJOR: MODERN DANCE
I'm going to keep it forever.
KOREA NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF ARTS
So which was
the hardest mountain to climb?
Seoraksan. I don't even
want to pee in its direction, Dad.
Then, I guess the Seoraksan episode
will be the longest.
Gosh, he knows very well.
Even his father knows very well.
Well, I think the difficulty
should increase as you go.
Dad!
I thought they'd climb seven peaks a day.
Sir!
But you said they only hiked three peaks.
FEELING BETRAYED
This is what the viewers want.
I thought he'd take our side.
I mean, it's his son hiking.
You know how fathers are.
They think their sons must do
military service and go through hardships.
We once went to the Chung-Ang University
student festival to see you.
-You did?
-Yes, a few years ago.
WENT TO WATCH HIM 3 YEARS AGO
Did you have a beard back then?
-I didn't.
-He didn't.
-It was long ago then.
Do you like any of his songs?
I do. My favorite is "Tree."
-Thank you, sir.
-Sing it for him.
PERFORMS RIGHT AWAY
Hold on. I didn't record it.
Could you do it again, please?
-I'm sorry.
-All right.
We haven't seen him sing either.
STARTING OVER
SINGING IN EARNEST
That was awesome.
He said he never sings on variety shows.
He never sings.
If someone's parents ask,
I do it right away.
That was our first time hearing him.
-Really?
-I've never seen it happen before.
-If you come again next time…
-Of course.
-I'll prepare a good meal for you.
-Thank you.
After eating your food,
my fear of singing live
just disappeared.
It was my first time.
-Have you heard him sing before?
-No.
He didn't sing even when I turned on
the karaoke machine in Jeju.
Why would I sing for you guys?
Think about it.
After such a nice meal, how could I not?
Today was a first.
I came out of the bathroom right away.
-"Why is he suddenly singing?"
-"What's happening?"
Interesting.
Now, I'm getting curious.
I want to meet Chae-min's parents.
I saw Dowoon
video calling his parents yesterday.
Then, for Season 2,
let's visit the members' houses.
And eat home-cooked meals.
"Have a Home-cooked Meal!"
That's a good idea.
AFTER ENJOYING THE MEAL,
THEY CLEAR THE TABLE TOGETHER
Oh, no. It's all right.
It's not hot.
It was really good.
-It's been a while since I ate this much.
-Same for me.
-This is what a meal should be.
-Right.
We've been eating pretty well.
-But this was so delicious.
-Right.
THE MEAL LEFT A LASTING IMPRESSION
The food was amazing.
And for dessert,
this is called Ulsan jjondeugi.
You make them like this. I'll put them in.
They'll stick.
PULLING THEM APART INTO SEPARATE STRIPS
THE SEASONING IS A MIXTURE
OF RAMYEON SEASONING AND SUGAR
SHAKE THE JJONDEUGI WITH SEASONING
TO MIX THEM WELL, AND IT'S DONE
Oh, that's it.
-What's this?
-Mom, did you put on the seasoning?
I did but only put a little on purpose.
We should add some more.
He's being stubborn again.
There's a reason why she made it that way.
I guess I need to discipline him more.
Next time Tarzzan comes home,
he'll be at the door and say,
"Mother, Father, I'm home."
I'll teach him to do that.
Just make him visit.
Okay, I'll send him here
by courier service.
Use your hands to rip them apart.
TARZZAN'S MOM'S ULSAN JJONDEUGI
I see. Eating it this way is good too.
There's a seasoning for this?
It's good.
You can't stop eating it.
After school,
there was no better snack than this.
IT FILLS TARZZAN WITH NOSTALGIA
SHE EVEN PREPARED CAKES AND FRUITS
-One per person?
-Thank you.
Gosh, the presentation.
1 PLATE PER PERSON
You should take a photo
and share it on your social media.
You can title it as "Tarzzan-kase."
I think we should go hiking right now.
Because of the calories.
EQUALS CALORIES FOR 3 PEAKS
Thank her with a deep bow after we go.
Okay.
-For real?
-Yes, for real.
Has the next mountain been decided yet?
-It has.
It's Jirisan.
Oh no!
Seriously, ma'am, once you watch the show,
you'll hate Producer Nah.
It'll break your heart.
Oh no.
SHE ALWAYS WORRIES ABOUT HER ONLY SON
-It's really tough.
-Tell him no.
Please tell him no.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to hear this.
-Finally, someone's taking our side.
-Finally.
She's the first adult on our side.
I've been waiting for so long.
Have you learned anything?
No.
-Nothing at all.
-Really?
But on the Yeongnam Alps yesterday…
I thought it was nice
for the very first time. It was beautiful.
The weather was nice, and it wasn't snowy.
You know, we had always hiked
snowy mountains before that.
But it wasn't snowy yesterday.
-Now that we've eaten a lot of food…
-Right.
I think we should go
so that Tarzzan can spend
some time with his parents.
All right.
-Thank you for the food.
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you for coming.
-Thank you.
Before we go, I should tell you
I thought you were his sister at first.
Thank you!
You look so young.
Darn, you beat me to it.
Bye, sis.
-See you later, guys.
-Goodbye.
Bye.
-Bye. Thank you.
-Thank you.
Goodbye.
-Bye.
-Keep in touch.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
DESCEND CLUB'S
ULSAN EXPEDITION ENDS
THANK YOU FOR THE MEAL, TARZZAN
IT WAS THE BEST
SAY THANKS TO YOUR PARENTS AND AUNT
THANKS FOR COMING, GUYS
DID YOU BOW TO THEM YET?
I DID AND HERE'S THE PROOF!
A MONTH LATER
AS SPRING DEEPENS IN MARCH
AND THE LONG WINTER
MELTS AWAY LITTLE BY LITTLE
DESCEND CLUB'S LAST HIKE
IS JUST A DAY AWAY
IT'S TIME TO LEAVE NOW
FOR JIRISAN
SEOUL MANNAMUI GWANGJANG SERVICE AREA
EXPRESSWAY REST STOP
THEY'LL MEET HERE AND LEAVE TOGETHER
TAKE A HIKE!
VIP SERVICE FOR JIRISAN
Car-the is here. Hello.
CAR, THE GARDEN ARRIVES FIRST
-Hi.
-Do we need crampons?
Yes. I think we'll need them.
It's still snowy at high altitudes.
Does anyone take pills for hair loss?
Why?
Didn't the hair on the top of my head
look less dense on camera?
I didn't notice it at all.
-Isn't there enough?
-The top of my head…
THE CAMERA SUDDENLY RISES
It's starting to thin.
Why are you filming that?
Right now, I have some product on.
From Etude House…
I put that on my hair.
Hello.
-How have you been?
-Good.
CHAE-MIN SOON ARRIVES
I think you've lost weight.
I've been on a diet. I run these days.
-Running?
-Yes.
To hike better?
GLARES
TURNS INTO A TYRANT
I've forgotten what this feels like.
THEY WAIT FOR DOWOON AND TARZZAN
ON THE BUS
Hello, Jung-won.
You look cool today.
This is the last one.
I thought I should dress for the occasion.
I was wondering why you guys
seemed to be in a good mood.
It was because this is the last one.
The bus is nice too.
THEY'RE MORE CHEERFUL THAN USUAL
How long is the round-trip hike
for Jirisan?
It's about nine to ten hours.
How hard is it?
He's already showing
an interest in the hike.
How should I put it?
Car-the is so passionate.
You know what I found so funny
about myself?
My close friends
suggested that we go hike
Gwanaksan Mountain.
But I acted arrogant.
HE'S A TRUE HIKER NOW
Tarzzan has just arrived.
Is Tarzzan here?
TARZZAN ARRIVES
AND DOWOON TOO
-You look happy.
-Hello.
-Chae-won, long time no see.
-Dowoon.
-It's been a while.
-Let's never hike again.
You must've been dying to go hiking.
-This is the last one.
-I know, right?
How have you been?
Well, I've been waiting for today.
I'm sure the production crew
has been eager for this day too.
ENTERING CONFIDENTLY
This is the last one!
HE CAN'T HIDE HIS EXCITEMENT
Hey, it's the last one.
THE LAST HELLO TO THE SOUND MIXER
He looks so excited.
-Hey.
-Hi, Jung-won.
EVERYONE'S GATHERED IN A GOOD MOOD
Why am I so upbeat today?
Gosh, I'm so corny!
What time will we start tomorrow?
Will you tell us now?
We're thinking of leaving at 6:00 a.m.
But that's a bit too early.
Come on, it's not that early.
-So it takes about nine hours?
-Yes.
IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG HIKE YET AGAIN
It's about average.
SUPER POSITIVE SINCE IT'S THE LAST HIKE
Yes, you're right.
Guys, this is the last hike.
Let's say goodbye with a smile.
WANTS TO END WITH NO HARD FEELINGS
I don't think you'll ever see them again.
You're planning to never see them again?
LIKE SOMEONE ABOUT TO QUIT THEIR JOB
I've never seen you
in such a good mood during a shoot.
Since it's the last day, I followed
Channel Fullmoon on social media.
D.DDABLUE FOLLOWS YOU
Everyone, these are souvenirs for you.
These are cute.
You can each have your own character.
HANDS OUT THE SHOW'S MERCHANDISE
I think that's me.
This place is nice!
WHEREVER DESCEND CLUB GOES
WE GO
WHEREVER DESCEND CLUB CLIMBS
WE CLIMB
CREATURES OFFICIALLY VERIFIED
BY TAKE A HIKE!
MAIN PLACES THEY APPEAR
ARE SNOWY MOUNTAINS
LET US INTRODUCE THESE COLORFUL YETIS
RED
HE'S MUCH BIGGER THAN THE OTHERS
HIS FACE IS COVERED BY A YELLOW BEARD
BUT DON'T JUDGE A BOOK BY ITS COVER
HE'S SENSITIVE AND LOVES TREES
RED LIKES SINGING MORE THAN HIKING
YELLOW
IF YOU HEAR AN EXCITING BEAT WHILE HIKING
THEN IT'S YELLOW
PLAYING THE DRUMS WITH ROCKS
USUALLY HAS WARM AND BRIGHT EYES
AND QUIETLY CLIMBS MOUNTAINS
EVEN WHEN IT'S WINDY
BUT HE ACTUALLY DREAMS OF GOING OUT TO SEA
FOR YELLOW, THE OCEAN IS MORE BEAUTIFUL
THAN THE MOUNTAINS
PINK
WITH WISTFUL EYES
AND LONG LEGS
THE VERY HANDSOME PINK
BE CAREFUL OF PINK WHILE HIKING
HIS HANDSOME FACE AND ELOQUENT SPEECH
MIGHT BEWITCH YOU
PINK IS A YETI MORE BEAUTIFUL
THAN THE MOUNTAIN RIDGES
BLUE
HE'S AN ACCOMPLISHED MOUNTAIN DANCER
AND CLIMBS MOUNTAINS TO THE BEAT
HIS CHARM OF BEING UNPREDICTABLE
MAKES HIM LOVED BY ALL THE OTHER YETIS
BLUE IS FILLED WITH BRIGHT ENERGY
These are so cute.
You can attach them to your bags.
Why are the hands stuck together?
They're magnetic.
IMPRESSED
-You can attach them to your bags.
-It's cute.
Yours has a bag.
Why does mine have a bag?
That's a song pouch.
A song pouch?
And it becomes a trail food pouch
when it hikes.
I see. For songs.
Dowoon's has sticks it holds in its hands.
-These are the sticks?
-Yes.
DRUMSTICKS FOR THE DRUMMER
Don't lose them.
There are four though.
-They're spares.
-Extra sticks.
Spares…
Awesome.
Mine has long hair.
-Here.
-Yes, long hair.
What about Chae-min's?
"Pretty as a flower."
This is a flower?
We put a flower since he's handsome.
I was looking for its features.
And yours is likely the tallest one.
-It's long.
-Really? Let me compare.
It is.
-Wait, it really is longer.
-Right.
Let me compare it with yours too.
Yours should be a bit taller.
But yours has more stuffing inside.
-Inside? You're right.
-Right?
It's pretty stuffed.
-There's a lot more inside.
-Yes.
I wish it were bigger.
BLUE BEING PLAYFUL
I CAN'T BE OUTDONE
GOOD FRIENDS
BLUE AND PINK
We go hiking tomorrow?
Yes, tomorrow.
THE DAY BEFORE THE LONG-AWAITED LAST HIKE
You've hiked really high
and difficult mountains so far.
But for this last one,
Jirisan is as high and difficult to climb
as Seoraksan and Hallasan.
So we've prepared
some places for relaxing.
DONGUIBOGAM VILLAGE
LOCATED AT THE FOOTHILLS OF JIRISAN
THE BIGGEST TRADITIONAL MEDICINE
THEME PARK IN KOREA
WHERE THE SACRED SPIRIT OF JIRISAN FLOWS
AND THE WARM SCENT
OF MEDICINAL HERBS CAPTIVATES
SANCHEONG
SANCHEONG DONGUIBOGAM VILLAGE
IN SOUTH GYEONGSANG PROVINCE
-Donguibogam Village?
-Yes.
-Isn't it related to Heo Jun?
-It is.
He's very knowledgeable.
Doesn't everyone know that much?
Shouldn't everyone know that?
MANNAMUI GWANGJANG SERVICE AREA
TO SANCHEONG DONGUIBOGAM VILLAGE
THEY ARRIVE AT THEIR LAST BASE CAMP
AFTER 3 HOURS
We're now at Donguibogam Village.
THEY ARRIVE AT DONGUIBOGAM VILLAGE
Here at Donguibogam Village,
we've prepared a three-piece
traditional medicine package for you.
First, boiled black pork
with medicinal herbs for your stamina.
Next, a cozy Korean medicine hotel.
And finally, to help your tired feet
recover from hiking,
a traditional medicine foot bath.
Is there anything like
"hit you with one punch"?
WHICH ONE WILL THEY BE HIT WITH FIRST?
BOILED PORK WITH MEDICINAL HERBS
FOR ENERGY
-Black pork.
-Jeongol.
Hello.
Look at the steam coming out.
It looks so good.
Gosh, this looks delicious.
A FULL SPREAD OF JIRISAN BLACK PORK
WITH MEDICINAL HERBS
BOILED BLACK PORK WITH MEDICINAL HERBS
BOILED WITH VARIOUS MEDICINAL HERBS
SO FULL OF FLAVOR
THE STEAMING DISH
WAITING NEXT TO THE BOILED PORK
BLACK PORK JEONGOL WITH MEDICINAL HERBS
WHITE BROTH WITH THE FLAVOR
OF MEDICINAL HERBS
There's a lot of meat.
THEY EAT THE BOILED PORK FIRST
WHILE THE JEONGOL COOKS
It's good.
TRYING A PIECE OF BOILED BLACK PORK
YUM
It's good.
HOW BOILED BLACK PORK WITH MEDICINAL HERBS
IS RELATED TO HIKING
1. CONTAINS PROTEIN
WHICH HELPS MAINTAIN MUSCLE MASS
I can taste the medicinal herbs.
2. CONTAINS COLLAGEN FOR STRENGTHENING
IMMUNE SYSTEM AND KEEPING SKIN HEALTHY
YUM
3. CONTAINS JUJUBES, GARLIC, AND GINGER
TO IMPROVE BLOOD CIRCULATION
IN ONE BITE
Traditional medicine kimchi.
4. CONTAINS PROBIOTICS AND FIBER
FOR SMOOTH BOWEL MOVEMENTS
The kimchi is good.
BLACK PORK JEONGOL WITH MEDICINAL HERBS
HAS BEEN COOKED PERFECTLY
-Aren't these mung bean sprouts?
-They are.
Right? Gosh, I love mung bean sprouts.
AMAZED
The broth is so good.
Damn, why is it so good?
Gosh.
Damn.
Gosh, it's amazing.
Gosh.
This is so good.
-Did you drink last night?
-No, I didn't.
THE JEONGOL REALLY HITS THE SPOT
Which was harder
between Hallasan and Jirisan?
I didn't climb Jirisan and just saw
pictures from the scouting trip.
Okay.
Gosh, the sea of clouds was so…
It's the most beautiful mountain
I've ever seen.
THE DAY OF THE SCOUTING TRIP ON JIRISAN
Gosh, this is so cool.
It's like where immortal hermits hang out.
THANKS TO THE INCREDIBLE SEA OF CLOUDS,
THE VIEW LOOKS LIKE A PIECE OF KOREAN ART
We saw a sea of clouds on Hallasan.
Right, on Hallasan.
It was more moving since we could see it
in a 360-degree, panoramic view.
It'll be more moving
because it's the last one.
Seriously. That would make me moved.
What did Netflix say
when they saw us hiking?
I bet people who watch
will be frustrated too.
-No, not at all.
-Really?
You know how they feel?
"Thank goodness I'm not there."
Like, "I'm so thankful
to be safe and warm in my room."
Do they think, "They're so pitiful"?
SO PITIFUL?
LET'S REVIEW WHAT DESCEND CLUB HAS DONE
1. SEORAKSAN TRAINING
"WITHOUT A DOUBT THE WORST HIKE EVER"
-TARZZAN
2. WATCHING THE SUNRISE ON TAEBAEKSAN
"I DIDN'T GET ENOUGH SLEEP"
-LEE CHAE-MIN
3. HALLASAN BAENGNOKDAM
"DON'T TAKE THE GWANEUMSA TRAIL"
-DOWOON
SEONGPANAK TEAM, 19 KM
GWANEUMSA TEAM, 18 KM
4. THE YEONGNAM ALPS' 3-PEAK CHALLENGE
"IT'S A KIND MOUNTAIN"
-CAR, THE GARDEN
ACCUMULATED DISTANCES FROM THE FOUR HIKES
KOREAN MEDICINE HOTEL
A WARM AND COZY ONDOL ROOM
AND 4 SITTING MATS SET ON ONE SIDE
All right, time for a game.
NATURALLY SITS DOWN
Why did you sit?
Do you even know what we're doing?
A game!
I know!
We're sitting on the floor?
THE EARTH ARCADE FAN ALSO ENTERS
I know!
EPISODE 7'S ZZAN OF TAR
AND MR. KIM UI-HAN ENTER TOO
-We're playing a game.
-Yeah, a game.
First off, congratulations.
It's the final shoot.
But we have another piece of good news,
so we asked to see you here.
Once all of you finish hiking Jirisan
during tomorrow's shoot,
you will have reached about 70 km.
We want to congratulate you on that first.
SEORAKSAN, TAEBAEKSAN
HALLASAN, YEONGNAM ALPS, JIRISAN
Hiking 70 km isn't an easy feat at all.
And when our series began,
we promised you something.
If you reach 100 km…
He said we could change the show.
If you reach 100 km,
we'll give you the right to change
the theme of our show as you like.
IF THEY REACH 100 KM,
THEY CAN CHANGE THE SHOW
For example, what do you want to do?
I want to go on vacation with them.
Take a Vacation!
That'd be great.
I think we'll find
answers to that quickly.
A lot faster than hiking?
HE LIKES TRAVELING
I see. What about Car-the?
What I want to do?
-Just off the top of my head?
-Yes.
I just want to rest and hang out.
Take a Rest and Hang Out!
For the rest of your life?
I just want to hang out.
To tell you the truth,
except for the hiking,
I really like this show.
A HIKING SHOW WITHOUT HIKING IS GOOD
I think this would be good.
Take a Rest in Bed and Stay Home!
Something like that.
THE MINISTER OF TRANSPORT
DOESN'T WANT TO MOVE
Anyway, if you happen to reach 100 km,
we'll do one of the things you guys want
in the next season.
But I don't think
100 km was ever possible.
Then, you can't keep your promise.
So we're going to give you the last chance
-to reach 100 km.
-What?
Once again, like last time,
we'll play a simple game
wagering kilometers.
We're giving you a chance
to reach 100 km today.
Damn it!
If you earn 30 km today,
we'll do the type of show you want.
If you don't, Season 2 will also be…
HIKING AGAIN
But we have nothing to lose.
We're already at 70 km anyway,
and today's the last day,
so it doesn't matter if we lose it all.
This is true.
We're offering you a good deal.
Okay.
Last time, if you bet 1 km,
the return was 1 km.
We'll double the return this time.
If you bet 1 km, you can earn 2 km.
If you bet 5 km, you can earn 10 km.
If you bet 10 km, you can earn 20 km.
If we lose, we give away 10 km.
But if we win, we get 20 km?
Yes, that's right. It's such a great deal.
-But the game must not be easy.
-Right.
-Then, can I tell you about the game?
-Yes.
I don't feel confident though.
MR. KIM UI-HAN IS WORRIED
Dowoon likes this game so much.
-He's good.
-Right.
Let's play "Finish the Phrase."
We're going to lose everything today.
UI-HAN LOOKS SAD
The category is
proverbs.
-I'm not good with proverbs.
-Proverbs…
THE YOUNGER MEMBERS
ARE SURPRISINGLY NOT CONFIDENT
I really don't know any proverbs.
I'm really bad with them.
You can practice. Start with Car-the.
-Kill two birds…
-With one stone.
Yes, like that.
-Get two for…
-Trimming branches.
-What was that, Dowoon?
-"Trimming cheese"?
-Trimming branches.
-"Trimming branches"?
A PROVERB FOR PLANT OWNERS
Hold on, stop it. Save it for later.
That was funny.
ON ANOTHER LEVEL AGAIN TODAY
Get two for what?
FOR THE PRICE OF ONE
Trimming branches?
This is a big problem.
You and I didn't know.
Right, I didn't know either.
AN UNEXPECTED VARIABLE
What's funny is,
young people don't know
proverbs these days.
-We don't.
-Of course not.
So close…
So close?
It was something about distance.
And almost there?
They're really bad.
I'm really bad with proverbs.
So close, yet so far.
How much will you bet?
-This is the first round.
-We'll bet 0.5 km.
A DROP IN THE OCEAN
Hey, we'll definitely lose.
So, 0.5 km.
You're betting 0.5 km?
AN EMBARRASSING AMOUNT
Yes, we'll bet 0.5.
It's because…
We have our reasons.
So please be understanding.
-So you'll bet 0.5 km?
-Yes.
Still, we can earn 1 km if we win.
Okay, we'll start off simple
and bet 0.5 km.
Shall we start?
With 0.5 km on the line,
is Car-the going first?
-Yes.
-It's for 0.5 km.
All right.
Do you want to switch seats with me?
Do you want just one turn?
I am still a bit older than you, so…
SWITCHING SEATS
I'm counting on you, Dowoon.
Here we go.
It'd be better for us to switch too.
Getting at least two right's better.
SWITCHING SEATS
Since the category is proverbs,
it's in order of age now.
-Are you ready?
-I was looking back on my life.
Proverbs usually come
from life experiences.
THEY ONLY GET 10 CHANCES
Okay, let's go.
BETTING 0.5 KM
Okay, here come the proverbs.
As you sow…
-So shall you reap.
-Correct!
Bad news…
-Travels fast.
-Correct!
Hold on.
Appearances can be…
-Deceiving.
-Correct!
Very good.
Where there's smoke…
-There's Santa Claus.
-Wrong!
Hey, come on!
-There's Santa Claus.
-Wrong!
SANTA CLAUS?
Hey, come on!
Hey, it's about proverbs!
Proverbs.
What kind of proverb has Santa Claus?
I know Netflix is headquartered
in another country,
but it's a Korean proverb.
How could you say "Santa Claus"?
Wait, what's the answer?
Where there's smoke…
-There's fire.
I'm doing pretty well.
The older members are a bit better.
THE YOUNGEST FEELS
MORE AND MORE EMBARRASSED
Smoke usually comes from a chimney,
so you thought of Santa Claus?
I'm pretty imaginative.
SMOKE TO CHIMNEY TO SANTA CLAUS
I do understand where he's coming from.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT, IT'S KIND OF CUTE
Now, you have lost 0.5 km each.
LAUGHS
It's good that we only bet 0.5.
Okay, good.
WISE CHOICE
-Will you bet 0.5 km again?
-Yes.
-Just 0.5.
-Come on, let's go big.
Let's go with 0.7. then.
Hey, 0.7 makes us look a bit petty.
-It looks bad.
-Okay, make it 1 km.
"It looks bad."
Betting 0.7 is ridiculous.
So, 1 km then?
-Yes.
-Yes, 1 km.
Okay, we'll speed things up.
There will be no pauses this time.
Car-the will go first.
Experience is the best…
-Teacher.
-Correct.
Betrayal comes from those…
-You trust the most.
-Correct.
You can spot potential…
-I don't know this.
-Wrong!
-You've never heard of it before?
-Never.
"You can spot potential"?
At an early age.
He's good.
But it does make sense.
From an early age,
you can see one's potential.
UNDERSTANDS AFTER HEARING IT
Potential?
Young people really don't use
proverbs these days.
HE DIDN'T KNOW
We lost 1 km?
We won't win anything at this rate.
Even if it's a one-way trip,
I don't think they'll succeed.
Probably not.
Hold on. If it's one-way, maybe…
You can't take back what you say.
What?
One successful pass counts.
-Was that a proverb just now?
-Yes.
"You can't take back what you say."
A GENIUS WITH PROVERBS
-Really?
-You said one.
It's no use crying over spilled milk.
-Let's try a one-way trip.
-Let's do it.
How much will you bet?
-Let's bet big.
-Maybe 2 km?
-Hold on. No.
-Are you confident?
-Then, 3 km?
-3 km?
Are you confident? Tarzzan?
I'm not confident at all.
I'm telling you in advance.
STRENGTHS
I'M HONEST
-Then, let's bet 2 km.
-2 km?
Just in case because it's one pass.
Let's bet 2 km, and you go first.
You go first.
It's better if you get it over with first.
-Okay.
-If you fail, we can move on right away.
LOW EXPECTATIONS
Tarzzan, I believe in you.
BETTING 2 KM
Okay, here we go. Tarzzan will go first.
What goes around…
Comes around.
Correct!
A chest feeling fear…
Chae-min. A chest feeling fear…
-Three, two…
-Gets bigger!
Wrong!
-Wrong!
A TOTALLY UNEXPECTED WRONG ANSWER
What gets bigger?
Hey, what do you mean "chest gets bigger"?
SILENT
Why would you say "chest gets bigger"?
-Geez, Chae-min.
-Chae-min.
VERY FLUSTERED
You said "filling up," so…
-"Filling up."
-You heard "filling up"?
"Filling up"!
"A chest filling up"!
HE HEARD "A CHEST FEELING FEAR"
AS "A CHEST FILLING UP"
Didn't he say "filling up"?
It was "feeling," not "filling."
OH, NO…
You said, "A chest feeling fear"?
I heard it as, "A chest filling up."
FEELING WRONGED
Hold on. Did anyone know the answer?
Is it related to pirate tales
or something?
CHESTS TO PIRATE TALES
So, what's the answer?
"It's easily startled again."
"A chest filled with fear"?
If something scared you before,
seeing it again would startle you.
Like, "Oh my goodness!"
It's like the idiom
"once bitten, twice shy."
Isn't this a pronunciation problem then?
What are you talking about?
You two understood perfectly well.
ANYWAY…
Could you make sure to edit this?
I think it's going to look bad.
SINCE THEY'RE MUCH WORSE THAN EXPECTED…
This is worse than we thought.
-The category Tarzzan was confident in.
-What was it?
-Should we try brands?
-Brands? Okay.
Not just any brand
but snacks or ice cream brands.
I'm confident with food.
CONFIDENT
I like eating.
For example, Shrimp…
Crackers.
-Product names? Okay.
-Yes.
All right, snacks and ice cream.
How much will you bet?
-Let's try 1 km.
-One or two? One?
Maybe 2 km?
-No, 1 km!
-Okay.
CALM DOWN
-We'll bet 1 km.
-1 km? Okay.
BETTING 1 KM
The category is snacks and ice cream.
-Honey Twist…
-Snack.
Correct.
-Couque…
-D'Asse.
Correct.
-Moist Choco…
-Chip Cookie.
Correct.
Tank…
-Top.
-Wrong!
Wait! I mean Tank Boy!
-Top.
-Wrong!
-"Tank top"!
-Wait! I mean Tank Boy!
Don't you know Tank Boy?
-"Tank top"?
-"Tank top"!
"Tank top"?
TANK TOPS ARE AS REFRESHING AS TANK BOY
"Tank top"!
GEEZ…
I'll turn around.
When I see Producer Nah's face,
my mind goes blank.
That's a good idea.
When I saw his face and he went, "Tank…"
I panicked.
Still, "tank top" is ridiculous!
-What's the answer?
-Tank Boy.
So you do know.
I knew it,
but I was overwhelmed by his face.
You were intimidated by him.
Yeah, I was.
Give us the second chance of losers.
"Second chance of losers"?
-A second chance game.
-A desperate plea.
Can't you let it slide just once?
Come on.
"Let this slide"!
Were you caught skipping class
or something?
That's what I used to always
say to my teacher.
All the time.
Kneeling down like this. "Please."
-Did it remind you of that?
-Yes.
But you know what?
They never let it slide.
In my experience, they never let it slide.
Damn it. I knew it,
but why did I get it wrong?
But it was really close this time.
Hey, let's try again. I can do better.
Okay.
Can I go first then?
-Okay.
-You come over here.
-He can just go first.
-Start from there.
HE UNDERSTANDS NOW
If we bet 2 km this time,
we can recoup all our losses.
-Tarzzan will go first.
-Okay.
-Category is snacks and ice cream.
BETTING 2 KM
-Here we go.
-You can do it.
-Bungeo…
-Ppang!
Wrong!
It does taste good.
Ppang!
Wrong!
It does taste good.
We know it's delicious.
But you know that's not the one.
It is delicious. Which flavor do you like?
Custard cream?
But isn't bungeo-ppang also correct?
It's a snack.
But that's not a brand.
-Right, the ice cream.
-It's Bungeo Samanco.
ALREADY LOST A TOTAL OF 6.5 KM
Hey, we've gotten all of them wrong.
CURRENT TOTAL KM
Let's play with the idea
that we can lose up to 10 km.
Okay, up to 10 km.
Gosh, this is so hard.
Why could I only think of
"ppang" as the answer?
Low risk, low return.
High risk, high return.
That was cool.
Why did you say that all of a sudden?
HE WAS JUST SHOWING OFF
-How much will you bet?
-We'll bet 1 km.
Let's bet 0.5 once again.
Let's catch our breath.
We'll bet 0.5. It's not looking good.
-How about restaurants? Franchises.
-Restaurants?
-Franchises.
-Franchises? I'm confident in that.
-Because you order food all the time.
-Right.
I have VIP status
on the food delivery app.
BETTING 0.5 KM
Franchise names.
Wonhalmeoni…
-Bossam.
-Correct.
Nolboo…
Bossam.
-Is that right?
-Yes, it exists.
Correct.
Hosigi…
-Double Chicken.
-Correct!
Jaws…
-Topokki.
-Correct.
-Dongdaemun…
-Tteokbokki!
-Yupdduk!
-Wrong!
I'll count it as correct.
ONLY THESE TWO ARE LEFT
There are two left?
Bareuda…
-Teacher Kim.
-Correct.
This is the last one.
IF TARZZAN GETS IT RIGHT, THEY WIN
-Haidi…
-Lao.
FIRST SUCCESS
We won 0.5!
-It's 0.5!
-No, 1 km.
THEY WIN A WHOPPING 1 KM
We did it!
-Good.
-We did well.
LOW RETURN
Haidilao was a difficult one.
But you knew it.
I happened to go
to Haidilao Hot Pot recently.
What does Bareuda Teacher Kim sell?
-Gimbap.
-I see.
Whenever I have a TV drama shoot,
I always go there
and buy food in the morning.
Since you bet 0.5 km,
you have won 1 km. Congratulations.
Hey, let's bet big now. It's time.
-Are we down 5.5 km now?
-Are you betting 5 km?
-Should we bet 6 km?
-Yeah.
-You want to recoup all your losses first?
-Yes.
We have four rounds left, right?
Yes, four.
Bet 6 km, and if we lose, bet 12 km.
If we lose again, bet 24 km.
-Let's do that.
-Okay, let's do it.
Okay, let's go.
VERY HIGH RISK PLAN
High risk, high return.
Okay, proverbs, snacks and ice cream,
fashion, or restaurants.
Isn't snacks and ice cream better?
You guys pick.
Let's do it.
Or should we save snacks and ice cream
for big bets later?
It's spicy stir-fried pork.
Right?
It's what I smell right now.
I'm sorry,
but please concentrate on the game.
HE ALWAYS CRACKS CHAE-MIN UP
I mean…
THE SMELL'S COMING IN THROUGH THE WINDOW
"Is it spicy stir-fried pork?"
DINNER: STIR-FRIED PORK & SEAWEED SOUP
From the restaurant?
Should we go with restaurants?
Since we smell food?
Okay, we choose restaurants.
RESTAURANT FRANCHISES
FINISH THE PHRASE
We'll bet 6 km and do restaurants.
Okay, then.
-Are you going first?
-Who should go first?
-You?
-I'll go first.
Then, it'll start and end with Car-the.
BETTING 6 KM
-Mom's…
-Touch.
Correct.
-Baskin…
-Robbins.
Correct.
-Five…
-Guys.
Correct!
-Tous les…
-Jours.
Correct!
HALFWAY THROUGH
Peli…
-Cana.
-Correct!
Myungrang…
-Jeotgal.
-Wrong!
TYRANT MODE ON
Hotdog!
What on earth is "Myungrang Jeotgal"?
It was Hotdog!
NOT MYUNGRANG JEOTGAL
IT'S POLLOCK ROE JEOTGAL
EMBARRASSED TO DEATH
Hey, what on earth is "Myungrang Jeotgal"?
Have you ever ordered from there?
If you have, then I'll understand.
I'm going to lose my mind.
Wando is so famous
for pollock roe jeotgal, so…
It is delicious.
I know it's delicious.
I suddenly want some.
A WRONG ANSWER BEFITTING OF FISHING FAN
-Chae-min looks so down.
-We were so close.
We were so close.
But it was so funny. Couldn't you count it
as correct? It was really funny.
Everyone laughed here.
-Jeotgal.
-Wrong!
IT IS TRUE THAT EVERYONE LAUGHED
Hotdog!
Yes, it was so funny.
Myungrang Hotdog. Darn it.
HE MADE UP A NEW PHRASE AGAIN
I remembered it too late.
Okay, so you've lost another 6 km.
I don't know anymore. Should we bet 20 km?
Let's do it.
Fashion brands and 20 km?
-Let's do it.
-Fashion brands and 20 km.
THEY ALL LOSE THEIR COOL IN THE END
Then, let me sit there.
I'll sit at the end.
Fashion brands are hard for me.
You go first.
FASHION BRANDS
"FINISH THE PHRASE"
How much have we lost in total?
-It's 11? 11.5 km.
-It doesn't matter if it's 10 or 20.
It's 11.5? Let's bet 12 km.
-Twelve?
-Yes.
TO BREAK EVEN
Are luxury brands included too?
Any fashion brand, including luxury ones.
Cartier.
-Right.
-Margiela.
Dowoon, if you say what you know now,
we'll have fewer options.
-Pretend you don't know.
-Okay.
You're smart about this kind of stuff.
So why do you never get anything right?
That was about proverbs.
Are you confident?
-Well, I… I am!
-Okay.
I'm sorry, but the way you're sitting…
Are you the Little Mermaid?
-We should relax to…
-Do it together. Okay. Like this?
We should straighten our legs?
Because when I watch Earth Arcade at home,
I watch it like this.
And I get many questions right.
I'm always like,
"How could they not know that?"
So we should do it as we do at home.
Is that so?
HOW CHAE-MIN SITS AT HOME
Why is Dowoon not…
Jeotgal was brutal.
LINGERING EFFECTS OF MYUNGRANG JEOTGAL
Car-the will go first.
BETTING 12 KM
-Uni…
-Qlo.
Correct.
Polo…
Ralph Lauren.
Damn it.
What? Why?
-What?
-Why are you flustered?
-I was going to say "Wrong."
-It was a buzzer beater.
I expected him to get it wrong.
Anyway, it's correct.
"Expected"!
Laco…
-Ste.
-Correct.
-Christian…
-Bale.
Wrong!
Bale.
BURSTING INTO LAUGHTER
GIGGLING
-Hey! Why did you think Batman?
-Dior!
-Right, Dior.
-Dior, Dowoon.
Hey, if you said Christian Louboutin…
Christian Bale?
Hey, he's a great actor. I know that.
But why say it here?
But I think he's an actor
as great as luxury brands.
Yes, that's right.
He is, but he's not a luxury brand.
He's a top-notch actor.
He's one with more value
than luxury brands.
-Christian Bale.
-I agree.
You agree? Then, it's correct?
No. It's not a fashion brand.
Wait, isn't Dior just "Dior"?
-Is it "Christian Dior"?
-Yes.
-That's the full name.
-Are they Christian?
-Hey, what…
-"Christian"!
"Christian" Dior.
I'm sorry.
We'll check that later.
SANTA CLAUS IS DYING FROM LAUGHTER
MYUNGRANG JEOTGAL IS ON ANOTHER LEVEL
Hey, could you check and see
if Christian Bale is Christian or not?
MYUNGRANG JEOTGAL
CHRISTIAN
-Did we lose 20 km?
-20?
Just now? Yes, about 17…
-It's 23.5 km?
-Okay.
Let's bet 24 km!
Should we just bet 30 km?
-Yes.
-30 km.
IT'S ALL OR NOTHING
But if we bet 30 km and lose,
we'll be left with almost 0 km.
Ending up with 0 km isn't all that bad.
VERY, VERY HIGH RISK
Can we take out a loan?
Do you have any collateral?
-What?
-Collateral for the loan.
I'll put up the next season as collateral.
The green light for next season?
HE'S NOT A LOAN SHARK
But you still have a lot left.
So how much will you bet?
Let's bet 30 km.
-Should we?
-Yes, and let's win.
We'll think about collateral later.
-Thirty?
-Yes, 30 km.
We'll be a slave to mountains.
-The category?
-You guys decide.
-Proverbs?
-Honestly, I'm confident in anything.
You guys pick.
I am too, except for proverbs.
Me too, except for proverbs.
I am confident in proverbs.
No, none of you are.
You should decide carefully.
Honestly, I prefer snacks or restaurants.
-Snacks or restaurants.
-Okay.
-Restaurants for me.
-Let's do that.
-Restaurants.
-30.
Try to recall everything you've eaten.
Don't say them out loud. Just recall them.
Car-the's really good.
He hasn't gotten anything wrong.
He's doing the "visualizing"
everyone talks about.
Okay.
NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT
I watched carefully,
and I saw noodles, rice, and beverages.
Even a Subway sandwich.
Okay, let's go.
FOCUSING AGAIN
This is practically the last round
if you run out of things to wager.
It feels like
I'm betting my entire fortune.
You've lost
the Hallasan and Yeongnam Alps hikes.
And the Seoraksan hike at this rate.
It's been a while since I've gone all in.
Here we go.
BETTING 30 KM
-Pop…
-Eyes.
Correct.
I was thinking Papa Recipe.
"Recipe"!
"Papa Recipe."
-I expected Papa John's.
-It's my favorite.
I expected Papa John's,
but Popeyes is correct.
-Sub…
-Way.
Correct.
Tore…
-Ore.
-Correct!
THAT WAS CLOSE
That brand collaborates with Moguchon.
I know.
Gosh, my palms are sweaty.
We'll go fast now.
NEXT UP
-Paris…
-Baguette!
Correct!
Myeong Ryun…
-Jinsa Pork Ribs!
-Correct!
-Please!
-Yoogane…
Chicken Galbi!
Yoogane…
LAST TURN
Chicken Galbi!
London…
Bagel!
Correct!
NOT THE FULL OFFICIAL NAME,
BUT STILL A GOOD ENOUGH ANSWER
My pants are falling down!
AN UNBELIEVABLE WIN
I've never been this happy before.
FEELING RELIEVED
We're really good with restaurants.
-I got a huge dopamine rush.
-This is crazy.
THE EXCITEMENT STILL LINGERS
Congratulations.
Now, we've recovered our losses.
After nine rounds,
-you were able to win 60 km.
-60 km.
Then, what happens?
CALCULATIONS GET COMPLICATED
You got "Chicken Galbi" right?
I thought you wouldn't get it.
-I had it two days ago.
-Wait.
This can't be right.
A MURMUR AMONG THE PRODUCTION CREW
We're over 100.
-We're over 100. We went over 100!
-Hold on!
-We went over 100!
-How many do we have?
WHAT HAPPENED?
-We went over 100.
-Wait.
We subtract 23.5 from 60.
-It's 96.5 km.
-I don't think they want us to win.
-It's 96.5!
-Hey!
Ninety… Hold on.
If we just hike Jirisan tomorrow,
-we'll go over 100.
-It's over.
-We have just 3.5 km left now.
-Yeah.
If we win again,
we won't have to hike tomorrow.
No. Let's go to Jirisan tomorrow.
-And end it there?
-Yes.
-Stomp it out?
-Let's end it.
-Stomp it out with our own feet?
-Let's end it!
Let's end it.
-Okay.
-Let's hike Jirisan tomorrow!
Okay, let's eat now.
TONIGHT'S DINNER
SPICY STIR-FRIED PORK
Okay, the end!
Let's stomp out
what we're sick and tired of.
-Let's break free.
-But this doesn't feel right.
So play another round?
-Let's make it 100.
-Well, look.
We're walking 12 km tomorrow anyway,
so we can lose until 88 km.
So, we only have to bet just 2 km,
nothing more, nothing less.
Just 2 km?
-Yes. If we win, it'll be 100.5.
-Okay!
Okay, let's bet 2 km then.
You want to bet 2 km and end it today?
Well, you can…
So, it's like a bonus round.
There's no pressure.
-Let's go.
-Which category?
Whatever you want.
Let's do fashion brands then.
-Sure.
-Fashion brands.
So, fashion brands?
FASHION BRANDS
"FINISH THE PHRASE"
BETTING 2 KM
-He'll go first.
-Right.
-Car…
-Tier.
Correct.
Doc…
-Martens.
-Correct.
-Monc…
-Ler.
Correct.
-Gentle…
-Monster.
Correct.
-Gior…
-Dano.
Correct.
-Chrome…
-Hearts.
Correct.
-Swar…
-Ovski.
We'll go home now!
SUCCESSFUL
THEY WON THE LAST 2 GAMES
We'll go home now!
THEY WIN ANOTHER 4 KM
My ex-girlfriend asked me to buy her that.
That's why I know.
"What? Swar what?"
"Swarovski!"
"What? Swarov?"
It's still in my head.
Swarovski.
That was perfect. 100.5 km.
You want the 0.5 back?
Let's just leave the 0.5 here.
Who knew this day would come?
All right.
What? Two people are still at 99.5?
-The Gwaneumsa team!
-Right, the Gwaneumsa team.
GWANEUMSA 99.5
-Hold on!
-We're at 100.5?
Hold on.
FOREVER SUFFERING
Dowoon and Tarzzan are at 99.5.
Dowoon and Tarzzan
don't have the right
to suggest ideas for the next season.
-Okay.
-You two can't.
Come on, let's play
another round for 0.5 km.
This is driving me crazy.
THEY CAN GO HIKE JIRISAN
The tenth round was the last one.
We'll discuss the next season's theme
only with Car-the and Chae-min.
Okay.
We can still listen to your opinions.
But just for taking
the Gwaneumsa trail, this is so unfair!
We went through a lot too.
That's the way life is, punk.
Thank you, everyone.
AND SO, DESCEND CLUB MET
THEIR 100 KM GOAL EARLY
THE NEXT DAY
THEY BEGIN THE LAST HIKE
TOWARD CHEONWANGBONG
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu